Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection MSS.040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I:Documentary Material, 40982
  - Subseries B: People, 40983
    - Canemaker, John: OTTO MESSMER & FELIX THE CAT, undated; 41238 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Canemaker, John: REMEMBERING WINSOR MCCAY, undated; 41237 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Canemaker, John: RISING STAR VIDEO logo, undated; 41236 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Canemaker, John: ROCKY HORRORSHOW commercial, undated; 41235 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Canemaker, John: SAFESEX, undated; 41234 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Canemaker, John: SEARCHING CA, ORKAZ VS. THEGYPSY MOTH, undated; 41233 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Canemaker,John: SILVER SCREEN PARTNERS IV, undated; 41232 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Canemaker, John: STREET FREAKS, undated; 41231 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Canemaker, John: UNIDENTIFIED FLYING PRANKSTERS, undated; 41230 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Canemaker, John: WHAT DO CHILDREN THINK OF WHENTHEYTHINK OF THE BOMB?, undated; 41229 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Canemaker, John: WHO'S THAT GIRL?, undated; 41228 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Canemaker, John: THEWIZARD'S SON, undated; 41227 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Canemaker, John: THEWIZARD'S SON, undated; 41226 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Canemaker, John: THE WORLD ACCORDING TO GARP, undated; 41225 (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
    - Canemaker, John: YOU DON'T HAVE TO DIE, undated; 41224 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Caniff, Milton, undated; 41223 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Catteneo, Tony ***see*** Wyatt, Ron, undated; 41222 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_9b31ef8f6044662bdad20d75932f12c0)
    - Clampett, Bob, undated; 41221 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Cohl, Emile, undated; 41220 (Box 8, Folder 56-58)
    - Cohl, Emile, undated; 41219 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Collins,Vincent, undated; 41218 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Cruikshank, Sally, undated; 41217 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Cruikshank, Sally, undated; 41216 (Box 40, Folder 350)
    - Cuba, Larry, undated; 41215 (Box 9, Folder 62.1)
    - Culhane,Shamus, undated; 41214 (Box 9, Folder 62.2)
    - Culhane, Shamus, undated; 41213 (Box 40, Folder 349)
    - David, Tissa-Films-RAGGEDY ANN &ANDY ***see*** Williams, Richard, undated; 41212 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - DeChomon, Segundo, undated; 41211 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Deitch, Gene, undated; 41210 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Deja, Adreas, undated; 41209 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Diaz, Ron, undated; 41208 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Disney,Walt: General, undated; 41207 (Box 9, Folder 66-67)
    - Disney, Walt: Joe Grant Study Collection, undated; 41206 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Disney, Walt: ALADDIN, undated; 41205 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Disney, Walt: ALICE INWONDERLAND, undated; 41204 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Disney, Walt: BEAUTY AND THE BEAST, undated; 41203 (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - Disney, Walt: THEBLACK CAULDRON, undated; 41202 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Disney, Walt: DONQUIXOTE, undated; 41201 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Disney, Walt:, Walt:DUMBO, undated; 41200 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Disney, Walt: DUMBO WORKDRAFT, 1941; 41199 (Box 23, Folder 231)
    - Disney, Walt:FANTASIA, undated; 41198 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, undated; 41197 (Box 27, Folder 261)
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA, undated; 41196 (Box 28, Folder 262-265)
    - Disney, Walt:THE FOX AND THE HOUND, undated; 41195 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Disney, Walt: THE JUNGLE BOOK, undated; 41194 (Box 10, Folder 75-76)
    - Disney, Walt: THE JUNGLE BOOK WORKDRAFT, 1967; 41193 (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Disney,Walt: THE LITTLE MERMAID, undated; 41192 (Box 10, Folder 77.1)
    - Disney,Walt: MAKE MINE MUSIC, undated; 41191 (Box 10, Folder 77.2)
    - Disney, Walt:MARY POPPINS, undated; 41190 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Disney, Walt:MELODY TIME, undated; 41189 (Box 10, Folder 79.1)
    - Disney, Walt: OLIVER& COMPANY, undated; 41188 (Box 10, Folder 79.2)
    - Disney, Walt: 101 DALMATIONS, 1996; 41187 (Box 20, Folder 247)
    - Disney, Walt: PETERPAN, undated; 41186 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Disney, Walt: PINOCCHIO, undated; 41185 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Disney, Walt: PINNOCHIO WORKDRAFT, 1940; 41184 (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Disney, Walt: RETURN TO OZ, undated; 41183 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Disney, Walt: SNOW WHITE & THE SEVENDWARFS, undated; 41182 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Disney, Walt:TRON, undated; 41181 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous Features, undated; 41180 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Disney, Walt: Miscellaneous Shorts, undated; 41179 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney-MGM ThemePark, undated; 41178 (Box 21, Folder 220-222)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney Animation Storyboarding, undated; 41177 (Box 23, Folder 230)
    - Disney, Walt: Dissertation - Robin Allen, 1993; 41176 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney-Animation Guides, undated; 41175 (Box 32, Folder 285)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Talent Devel. Discussion Group, undated; 41174 (Box 32, Folder 290)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1984-1995; 41173 (Box 32, Folder 297)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996; 41172 (Box 37, Folder 323-324)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996; 41171 (Box 38, Folder 325-331)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, 1932-1996; 41170 (Box 39, Folder 338)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Articles, undated; 41169 (Box 27, Folder 332)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Annual Report, 1992; 41168 (Box 39, Folder 340)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Correspondence, 1938-1955; 41167 (Box 39, Folder 341)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Student Paper: Disney and Gender, undated; 41166 (Box 39, Folder 342)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Uncompleted Film List, undated; 41165 (Box 39, Folder 343)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Disneyana Convention, 1996; 41164 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - Disney, Walt: Disney - Analysis: M. Mouse, et al., undated; 41163 (Box 41, Folder 366)
    - Dopff, Paul, undated; 41162 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Drouin, Jacques, undated; 41161 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Duesing, James, undated; 41160 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Dunning, George, undated; 41159 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Dunning, George, undated; 41158 (Box 40, Folder 351)
    - Dyer, Anson, undated; 41157 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - Edera, Bruno, undated; 41156 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - Emes, Ian, undated; 41155 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Engel, Jules, undated; 41154 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Engel, Jules, undated; 41153 (Box 40, Folder 358)
    - Enguster, Al, undated; 41152 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Fawdry, Richard, undated; 41151 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Fischinger, Oscar & Elfriede, undated; 41150 (Box 11, Folder 96-97.1)
    - Fischinger, Oscar & Elfriede, undated; 41149 (Box 33, Folder 298-301)
    - Fisher, Bud, undated; 41148 (Box 11, Folder 97.2)
    - Fitzsimmons, John A., undated; 41147 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Fleischer, Max & Dave, undated; 41146 (Box 11, Folder 98-99)
    - Foray, June, undated; 41145 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Freleng, Friz, undated; 41144 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Gardiner, Bob ***see*** Vinton, Will, undated; 41143 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - Gilliam, Terry, undated; 41142 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Godfrey, Bob, undated; 41141 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Golden, Books, undated; 41140 (Box 30, Folder 271)
    - Griffin, George, undated; 41139 (Box 12, Folder 104)
    - Grillo, Oscar, undated; 41138 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Gross, Anthony, undated; 41137 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Gross, Anthony, undated; 41136 (Box 40, Folder 360)
    - Hahn, Don, undated; 41135 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, undated; 41134 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Halas, John & Batchelor, Joy, undated; 41133 (Box 40, Folder 361)
    - Hall, David, undated; 41132 (Box 30, Folder 276)
    - Hand, David, undated; 41131 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Hawkins, Emery, undated; 41130 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Hench, John, undated; 41129 (Box 30, Folder 270)
    - Henson, Tex, undated; 41128 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Holland, Sylvia, undated; 41127 (Box 27, Folder 273)
    - Holland, Sylvia, undated; 41126 (Box 30, Folder 274)
    - Horvath, Ferdinand, undated; 41125 (Box 30, Folder 266-269)
    - Hubley, John & Faith, undated; 41124 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Hubley, John & Faith, undated; 41123 (Box 40, Folder 347)
    - Huemer, Richard, undated; 41122 (Box 12, Folder 112-113)
    - Hult, Lars - Arne, undated; 41121 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Hurter, Albert, undated; 41120 (Box 30, Folder 272)
    - Jittlov, Mike, undated; 41119 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Johnston, Ollie ***see*** Thomas, Frank, undated; 41118 (Box 12, Folder data_value_missing_7136a45ae22eff99e5b588aa6fe32f0e)
    - Jones, Bob, undated; 41117 (Box 30, Folder 277)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated; 41116 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated; 41115 (Box 31, Folder 278-283)
    - Jones, Chuck, undated; 41114 (Box 27, Folder 284)
    - Kahl, Milt, undated; 41113 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Katzenberg, Jeffrey, undated; 41112 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Khitruk, Fedor, undated; 41111 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Kijowicz, Miroslaw, undated; 41110 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Kimball, Ward, undated; 41109 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - Kinney, Jack, undated; 41108 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Klein, I., undated; 41107 (Box 13, Folder 122)
    - Kopp,Harry, undated; 41106 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Korty, John, undated; 41105 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Lantz, Walter, undated; 41104 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - Lantz, Walter, undated; 41103 (Box 40, Folder 362)
    - Leach, John & Rankin, Jean, undated; 41102 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Leaf, Caroline &Soul, Veronika, undated; 41101 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Leaf, Caroline, undated; 41100 (Box 40, Folder 363)
    - Leigh, Douglas, undated; 41099 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Leiva, Stephen Paul, undated; 41098 (Box 32, Folder 291)
    - Levitow, Abe, undated; 41097 (Box 32, Folder 287)
    - Lieberman, Jerry, undated; 41096 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Lounsbery, John, undated; 41095 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Lye, Len, undated; 41094 (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Lye, Len, undated; 41093 (Box 40, Folder 359)
    - McCay,Winsor ***see*** Box 17, undated; 41092 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_619890d5c391120d0cc1720a87206021)
    - McClaren,Norman, undated; 41091 (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - McClaren,Norman, undated; 41090 (Box 41, Folder 365)
    - Markewich, Arthur, undated; 41089 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Messmer, Otto ***see*** Box 7, Folder 39:Canemaker, undated; 41088 (Box 18, Folder 203-204)
    - John-Film-OttoMessmer & Felix the Cat], undated; 41087 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Miller, J.J., undated; 41086 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - Moniz, Ray W., undated; 41085 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - Moritz, William, undated; 41084 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - Moritz, William, undated; 41083 (Box 33, Folder 302-305)
    - Moritz, William, undated; 41082 (Box 35, Folder 306)
    - Morrison, Tammy ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated; 41081 (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_3e1f3b9d0b254ba7da5be45776a0ad26)
    - Moser, Frank ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated; 41080 (Box 35, Folder data_value_missing_63214c785ee9bec2457fa21f853f7952)
    - Mouris, Frank & Caroline, undated; 41079 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - Natwick, Grim[***see also: Box 18, Folder 203: Interview re: Otto Messmer], undated; 41078 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Natwick, Grim, undated; 41077 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - Nibbelink, Paul, undated; 41076 (Box 13, Folder 137)
    - Nielsen, Kay, undated; 41075 (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - Nordberg, Cliff, undated; 41074 (Box 32, Folder 292)
    - Norstein, Yuri, undated; 41073 (Box 14, Folder 138)
    - Noyes, Eliot, undated; 41072 (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - O'Neill, Pat, undated; 41071 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - Oriolo, Joe ***see*** Oversize Box 20., undated; 41070 (Box 18, Folder 204)
    - Padron, Juan, undated; 41069 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Pal, George, undated; 41068 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Park, Nick, undated; 41067 (Box 20, Folder 246)
    - Parker, Claire ***see*** Alexeieff, Alexander, undated; 41066 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_2aa446d864120069cc1d82022d491f4f)
    - Pies, Dennis, undated; 41065 (Box 14, Folder 143)
    - Pies, Dennis, undated; 41064 (Box 40, Folder 357)
    - Pitt, Suzan, undated; 41063 (Box 14, Folder 144)
    - Plympton, Bill, undated; 41062 (Box 40, Folder 353)
    - Potterton, Gerald, undated; 41061 (Box 14, Folder 145)
    - Protovin, Richard, undated; 41060 (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Protovin, Richard, undated; 41059 (Box 40, Folder 354)
    - Rankin, Arthur Jr. &Bass, Jules, undated; 41058 (Box 14, Folder 147)
    - Rankin, Jean ***see*** Leach, John, undated; 41057 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_e0b04995f5169ef009e3bd44ec9b37e5)
    - Reiniger, Lotte, undated; 41056 (Box 14, Folder 148)
    - Ren & Stimpy, undated; 41055 (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - Richter, Hans, undated; 41054 (Box 14, Folder 149)
    - Ring, Borge, undated; 41053 (Box 14, Folder 150)
    - Rose, Kathy, undated; 41052 (Box 14, Folder 151)
    - Rose, Kathy, undated; 41051 (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - Rybczynski, Zbigniew, undated; 41050 (Box 40, Folder 355)
    - Leon Schlesinger Productions, undated; 41049 (Box 32, Folder 288)
    - Schneider, Peter, undated; 41048 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Schwartz, Lillian, undated; 41047 (Box 14, Folder 152)
    - Sito, Thomas R., undated; 41046 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    - Solomon, Charles, undated; 41045 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Soul, Veronika ***see*** Leaf, Caroline, undated; 41044 (Box 16, Folder data_value_missing_80364b3da3da2791a150f0eeb04d0974)
    - Spafford, Dave, undated; 41043 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Sporn, Michael, undated; 41042 (Box 14, Folder 154)
    - Stapp, Philip, undated; 41041 (Box 14, Folder 155)
    - Sullivan, Pat***see*** Oversize Box 20, undated; 41040 (Box 18, Folder 208-208a)
    - Svankmajer, Jan, undated; 41039 (Box 40, Folder 356)
    - Swathe, Robert, undated; 41038 (Box 14, Folder 156)
    - Tenggren, Gustaf, undated; 41037 (Box 35, Folder 307)
    - Terry, Paul, undated; 41036 (Box 24, Folder 234-242)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston, Ollie, undated; 41035 (Box 14, Folder 157-158)
    - Thomas, Frank & Johnston,Ollie-Films-Nemo, undated; 41034 (Box 15, Folder 159)
    - Tytla, William, undated; 41033 (Box 15, Folder 160-161)
    - Tytla, William, undated; 41032 (Box 21, Folder 227-228)
    - Tytla, William, undated; 41031 (Box 23, Folder 229)
    - Unidentified Animation Notes, undated; 41030 (Box 32, Folder 296)
    - Vinton, Will & Gardiner, Bob, undated; 41029 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - Vujanovic, Branko & Zdenka, undated; 41028 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Vukotic, Dusan, undated; 41027 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Walker, Hal, undated; 41026 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - Ward, Jay, undated; 41025 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Washom, Ben, undated; 41024 (Box 32, Folder 286)
    - Weiss, William ***see*** Terry, Paul, undated; 41023 (Box 32, Folder data_value_missing_1dde24f3382785ad219ed39774db9094)
    - Whitney, James, undated; 41022 (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Whitney, John Sr., undated; 41021 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Williams, Richard-General, undated; 41020 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - Williams,Richard-Films-RAGGEDY ANN & ANDY, undated; 41019 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - Williams, Richard-Films-WHO FRAMED ROGER RABBIT?, undated; 41018 (Box 16, Folder 170-172)
    - Winkler, Margaret, undated; 41017 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Wong, Ty, undated; 41016 (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - Wyatt, Ron & Catteneo, Tony, undated; 41015 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - Canemaker, John- Books-WINSOR MCCAY, undated; 41014 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_6d698678c36df1ee133cebff866f5187)
    - Winsor McCay: Diary, 1908; 41013 (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Winsor McCay: Article: Animated Art., undated; 41012 (Box 17, Folder 181)
    - Winsor McCay: Article: How I Originated MotionPicture Cartoons., undated; 41011 (Box 17, Folder 182)
    - Winsor McCay: Art: Gertie the Dynosaur: (copy), undated; 41010 (Box 17, Folder 183-185)
    - Winsor McCay: Contracts, undated; 41009 (Box 17, Folder 186)
    - Winsor McCay: Correspondence to W.M., 1903-1955; 41008 (Box 17, Folder 187)
    - Winsor McCay: Correspondence: Milton Caniff, undated; 41007 (Box 17, Folder 188)
    - Winsor McCay: Typescript: "My Dayswith Winsor McCay," by John A. Fitzsimmons., undated; 41006 (Box 17, Folder 189)
    - Winsor McCay: Newsclips, undated; 41005 (Box 17, Folder 190-193)
    - Winsor McCay: Family History, undated; 41004 (Box 17, Folder 194)
    - WinsorMcCay: Toys, etc. based ON W.M. Drawings, undated; 41003 (Box 17, Folder 195)
    - Winsor McCay: John Canemaker's Book Proposal & Articles on W.M., undated; 41002 (Box 17, Folder 196-197)
    - Winsor McCay: W.M.: Little Nemo's Daddy - Unpublished Biography by Padric O'Glasain, 1941; 41001 (Box 25, Folder 243-244)
    - Winsor McCay: Art of W.M. - PhD Diss., 1976; 41000 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Canemaker, John-Books-FELIX, undated; 40999 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_b4fdb641663337e5f7298d86464875e7)
    - Computer discs (Felix the Cat), undated; 40998 (Box 18, Folder 200)
    - Interviews: Al Eugaster, 1989; 40997 (Box 18, Folder 201)
    - Interviews: Arthur Markewich, 1989; 40996 (Box 18, Folder 202)
    - Interviews: Otto Messner, 1975-1980; 40995 (Box 18, Folder 203-204)
    - Interviews, Diary, 1918-1919; 40994 (Box 18, Folder 205)
    - Interviews: GrimNatwick, 1989; 40993 (Box 18, Folder 206)
    - Interviews: Joe Oriolo, 1975; 40992 (Box 18, Folder 207)
    - Interviews: Sullivant, Pat, 1989; 40991 (Box 18, Folder 208-208a)
    - Interviews: Hal Walker, 1978,1989; 40990 (Box 18, Folder 209)
    - Felix the Cat: Research Materials, undated; 40989 (Box 19, Folder 210-213)
    - Book Typescript, undated; 40988 (Box 19, Folder 214-215)
    - Book Galleys, undated; 40987 (Box 19, Folder 216)
    - Correspondence, undated; 40986 (Box 20, Folder 217-221)
    - Oversize DocumentaryMaterials, undated; 40985 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_29a63c4fcfd4dd1f0426288030b127bc)
    - Disney - MGMTheme Park, undated; 40984 (Box 22, Folder 222-224)
- Series II: Graphic Material, 40918
  - Subseries C: Flip Books, 40919
    - Boxed set of 6 Flip Bookswith Brochure (Tony Eastman,Paul Glabicki, George Griffen, Roger Kukes, Sara Petty, KathyRose) Flames-Woman of the Year Rotoscope- Katonah Gallery Instruction Book The IncredibleMagic of Magic-Dance Lesson-Yves Brangolo Calarts-John Canemaker (2)-Ottawa '78(2)-Crayonite, 1978; 40930 (Box II.C.1, Folder data_value_missing_76147a025defe06d09c16b1a4d20d6e4)
    - Emile Cohl (2)-ShamusCulhane-John Dilworth, undated; 40929 (Box II.C.2, Folder 5)
    - Walt Disney "FlipBook" from the Art Corner (3), undated; 40928 (Box II.C.2, Folder 6)
    - Walt DisneyMoving Picture Flip Book (4), undated; 40927 (Box II.C.2, Folder 7)
    - Paul Dopff (4), undated; 40926 (Box II.C.2, Folder 8)
    - Paul Driessen (2)-James Duesing &Thomas Lenden-Oskar Fischinger, undated; 40925 (Box II.C.2, Folder 9)
    - PeterFoldes-Harold Friedman-John & Faith Hubley (3), undated; 40924 (Box II.C.2, Folder 10)
    - Jill & Al Jarnow-Miroslaw Kijowicz-Yoji Kuri-Vladimir Lehky, undated; 40923 (Box II.C.2, Folder 11)
    - Jan Lenica-Otto Messmer (2), undated; 40922 (Box II.C.2, Folder 12)
    - Marv Newland (3)-Sandy, undated; 40921 (Box II.C.3, Folder 13)
    - Gary Schwartz-B. Shackman-SHR Communications-Richard Williams, undated; 40920 (Box II.C.3, Folder 14)
- Series III: Book Collection, 1945-2012; 3 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains books and other printed materials donated with the collection.
  - Agel, Jerome. The Making of Kubrick's 2001, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts. AIGA/DFTV.002 Program, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Amidi, Amid. The Art of Pixar Short Films, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Andersen, Yvonne. Teaching Film Animation to Children, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Anima Mundi 2006 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Animation Journal, Fall 1994 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Animation Magazine, Vol. 1 Issue 1, 2/3, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Animation Magazine: May 2003, February 2004, July 2005 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Animatoon Vol. 12 no. 61, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Balázs, Béla. Theory of the Film, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Bogdanovich, Peter. Pieces of Time, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Bradbury, Ray. The Martian Chronicles, 1962 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Chaplin, Charles. My Autobiography, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - The Czechoslovak Film Institute - The Film Archive: Prague 1980 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - de Caso, Jacques, and Patricia B. Sanders. Rodin's Thinker, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - de Salvo, Donna, and Annetta Massie. Apocalyptic Wallpaper, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - de Salvo, Donna. Surrealism, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Disney Collection, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Fantoche, undated (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Feats of Clay, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Film Culture no. 61, 63-64, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Film History, vol. 5 no. 2, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Film Library Quarterly, vol. 11 nos. 1 2, 1978 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Forum des Images, Mars 2011 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - George Eastman House. Live Breathe Film, 2011 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 1, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 2, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 6, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 7, 2008 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 8, 2009 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 9, 2010 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 10, 2011 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 11, 2011 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Ghez, Didier. Walt's People - Volume 12, 2012 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Grafika Sto Je To, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Graham, F. Lanier. Hector Guimard, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - How, vol. I no. 3, 5; vol. II no. 1, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - How, vol. II no. 5; vol. III no. 5, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - J.J. Sedelmaier Productions, Inc. Ambiguously Gay Duo Comics, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Jung, Carl G. Man and His Symbols, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Lee, Sondra. I've Slept With Everybody, 2009 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Mast, Gerald, and Marshall Cohen. Film Theory and Criticism, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Magoo, McBoing Boing Modern Art, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Martin, André. Family Tree of the Origin and Golden Age of the American Cartoon Film 1906-1941, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - McKay, Winsor. Little Nemo in Slumberland, 1945 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - McKay, Winsor, and Jerry Kucia. Zagreb '82 Retrospectives, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - MoMA Film. December 2003 Film and Media Exhibitions (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - The Museum of Modern Art. Pixar: 20 Years of Animation, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Napolicomics, 7a Mostra Internazionale del Fumetto e del Cinema d'Animazione, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Open Roads: New Italian Cinema, 2001 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Ottawa International Animation Festival, 2011 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Otto Meismer Felix the Cat, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Pilling, Jayne. Cartoons the Movies, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Chris J. Between Genius Utter Illiteracy, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - San Francisco Silent Film Festival, 2012 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Sedona International Film Festival, 2009 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Stephenson, Ralph. The Animated Film, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Tortora, Matilde. Viaggi nell'animazione, 2008 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Tribute to Charles, 1990 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - The Vincent Astor Gallery. Margot Fonteyn in America: A Celebration, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - University Art Museum, University of Minnesota, Minneapolis. From Swedish Fairy Tales to American Fantasy: Gustaf Tenggren's Illustrations 1920-1970, 1986 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Woman of the Year, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 19)